<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>LeadsCalendar v1.0</title><link>//localhost:1313/docs/users/</link><description>Recent content on LeadsCalendar v1.0</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="//localhost:1313/docs/users/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Overview</title><link>//localhost:1313/docs/users/overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//localhost:1313/docs/users/overview/</guid><description>Introduction # Welcome to the LeadsCalendar documentation!
Overview of LeadsCalendar # LeadsCalendar is a sophisticated web application designed to streamline event creation processes while incorporating seamless payment processing functionalities. By integrating with Google Calendar, PayPal, and Binance Pay APIs, LeadsCalendar empowers users to effortlessly create events and complete payments within a unified platform.
Purpose # LeadsCalendar simplifies event creation and payment processing by integrating with Google Calendar, PayPal, and Binance Pay APIs.</description></item><item><title>Functionality</title><link>//localhost:1313/docs/users/key_features/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//localhost:1313/docs/users/key_features/</guid><description>Functionality of the LeadsCalendar Project # The LeadsCalendar project combines event creation and payment processing functionalities to provide users with a seamless experience. Here&amp;rsquo;s a detailed description of its functionality:
Event Creation:
Users can access the LeadsCalendar web application through a user-friendly interface. Upon logging in or signing up, users are presented with options to create new events. The event creation form typically includes fields such as event title, description, start date, end date, location, and any additional details.</description></item><item><title>Appendix</title><link>//localhost:1313/docs/users/appendix/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//localhost:1313/docs/users/appendix/</guid><description>Appendix # Glossary # API: Application Programming Interface JWT: JSON Web Token NoSQL: Not Only SQL, a type of database that provides a mechanism for storage and retrieval of data that is modeled in means other than the tabular relations used in relational databases. RESTful: Representational State Transfer, an architectural style for designing networked applications. OAuth: Open Authorization, an open standard for access delegation commonly used as a way for Internet users to grant websites or applications access to their information on other websites but without giving them the passwords.</description></item></channel></rss>